

Karl Francis Linget

Front-End Web Developer

Innovative, task-driven professional with 2+ years of experience in front-end web development. Eager and committed to learn any programming language and skillsets needed for the project completion. Educated, and practices industry standards such as clean coding.

	(+63)-9	45-	-32	2-1	116	i
_			, -	. •				

kflinget@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ francis-linget-a423bb176/

Skills

Intermediate Level

- HTML
- Javascript
- Typescript
- ReactJS
- NextJS
- VueJS
- Nuxt
- CSS
- TailwindCSS
- SASS
- Git

Novice Level

- Firebase
- Python
- C, C++

Work Experience

February 2023 to Present

NowServing Healthcare Corporation

Front-end Web Developer

- Mapped and create System Design in some projects
- Connection of backend with API
- Create user interfaces, write code, troubleshoot issues, and implement new features

February 2022 to June 2023

Freelance

Front-end Web Developer

- Creation of design and features according to client's specification
- · Connection of backend with API

July 2021 to August 2021

Pamantasan ng Lungsod ng Maynila

ICTO - System Development Division: Enhancement of CRS and (GSP) System

- Helped in debugging and polishing old System Design
- Helped in mapping and creation of System Design
- Responsible for adding new features
- Planned, created, and proposed new design for the Student Portal

Language

- English
- Tagalog

Education

Pamantasan ng Lungsod ng Maynila

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

Intramuros, Manila 2018-2023

Projects

L.A.M.E. Compiler

Requirement in one of our core subjects Stack: Python

Gamer's Lounge: Future of E-commerce

An e-commerce web application for one of our core subject's requirements Stack: ReactJS, CSS, Firebase Cloud Firestore, Stripe